<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Tung Kieu</title>
    <link>https://tungk.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Tung Kieu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://tungk.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://tungk.github.io/pages/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tungk.github.io/pages/profile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact-information&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Contact Information&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#contact-information&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Office&lt;/strong&gt;: (1) A.C. Meyers Vaenge 15, Room 2.095, Copenhagen, Denmark; (2) Selma Lagerlofs Vej 300, Room 3-2-05, Aalborg, Denmark&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: (1) tungkvt[at]cs[dot]aau[dot]dk; (2) kvttung[at]gmail[dot]com&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;biography&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Biography&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#biography&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am an Assistant Professor in the &lt;em&gt;Department of Computer Science&lt;/em&gt; at &lt;em&gt;Aalborg University&lt;/em&gt;. I am a faculty member in &lt;em&gt;Center for Data-Intensive Systems&lt;/em&gt;. I am also affiliated with the department&amp;rsquo;s team on Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning and the university&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Center on AI for the People&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publication</title>
      <link>https://tungk.github.io/pages/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tungk.github.io/pages/publication/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;selected-publication&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Selected Publication&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#selected-publication&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Buang Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Xiangfei Qiu, Chenjuan Guo, Jilin Hu, Aoying Zhou, Christian S. Jensen, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;An Encode-then-Decompose Approach to Unsupervised Time Series Anomaly Detection on Contaminated Training Data&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICDE&lt;/strong&gt; 2026 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nghiem Thanh Pham, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Duc-Manh Nguyen, Son Ha Xuan, Nghia Duong-Trung, and Danh Le-Phuoc. &lt;em&gt;SLM-Bench: A Comprehensive Benchmark of Small Language Models on Environmental Impact&lt;/em&gt;. International Conference on Empirical Methods in Natural Language Processing&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;EMNLP&lt;/strong&gt; 2025 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Huy Le, Nhat Chung, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Anh Nguyen, and Ngan Le. &lt;em&gt;BiMa: Towards Biases Mitigation for Text-Video Retrieval via Scene Element Guidance&lt;/em&gt;. ACM International Conference on Multimedia&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;MM&lt;/strong&gt; 2025 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duc Kieu, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Peng Han, Bin Yang, Christian S. Jensen, and Bac Le. &lt;em&gt;TEAM: Topological Evolution-aware Framework for Traffic Forecasting&lt;/em&gt;. International Conference on Very Large Data Bases&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;VLDB&lt;/strong&gt; 2025 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Miao Zhang, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;QCore: Data-Efficient, On-Device Continual Calibration for Quantized Models&lt;/em&gt;. International Conference on Very Large Data Bases&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;VLDB&lt;/strong&gt; 2024 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chenjuan Guo, Ronghui Xu, Yuan Ye, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Yan Zhao, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Efficient Stochastic Routing in Path-Centric Uncertain Road Networks&lt;/em&gt;. International Conference on Very Large Data Bases&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;VLDB&lt;/strong&gt; 2024 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Huy Le, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Anh Nguyen, and Ngan Le. &lt;em&gt;WAVER: Writing-style Agnostic Video Retrieval via Distilling Vision-Language Models Through Open-Vocabulary Knowledge&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Acoustics, Speech, and Signal Processing&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICASSP&lt;/strong&gt; 2024 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, Miao Zhang, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;LightTS: Lightweight Time Series Classification with Adaptive Ensemble Distillation&lt;/em&gt;. ACM International Conference on Management of Data&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;SIGMOD&lt;/strong&gt; 2023 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Xuanyi Dong, Shirui Pan, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;Triformer: Triangular, Variable-Specific Attention for Long Sequence Multivariate Time Series Forecasting&lt;/em&gt;. International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;IJCAI&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Shirui Pan, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;Towards Spatio-Temporal Aware Traffic Time Series Forecasting&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICDE&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, Chenjuan Guo, Christian S. Jensen, Yan Zhao, Feiteng Huang, and Kai Zheng. &lt;em&gt;Robust and Explainable Autoencoders for Time Series Outlier Detection&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICDE&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, Chenjuan Guo, Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, Yan Zhao, Yale Song, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Anomaly Detection in Time Series with Robust Variational Quasi-Recurrent Autoencoders&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICDE&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yan Zhao, Xuanhao Chen, Liwei Deng, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Bin Yang, Kai Zheng, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Outlier Detection for Streaming Task Assignment in Crowdsourcing&lt;/em&gt;. ACM The Web Conference&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;WWW&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Feiteng Huang, Kai Zheng, Bin Yang, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Unsupervised Time Series Outlier Detection with Diversity-Driven Convolutional Ensembles&lt;/em&gt;. International Conference on Very Large Data Bases&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;VLDB&lt;/strong&gt; 2022 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Bin Yang, and Sinno Jialin Pan. &lt;em&gt;EnhanceNet: Plugin Neural Networks for Enhancing Correlated Time Series Forecasting&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;ICDE&lt;/strong&gt; 2021 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Outlier Detection for Time Series with Recurrent Autoencoder Ensembles&lt;/em&gt;. International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;IJCAI&lt;/strong&gt; 2019 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;*)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Distinguishing Trajectories from Different Drivers using Incompletely Labeled Trajectories&lt;/em&gt;. ACM International Conference on Information and Knowledge Management&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;CIKM&lt;/strong&gt; 2018 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE A&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Outlier Detection for Multidimensional Time Series Using Deep Neural Networks&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE International Conference on Mobile Data Management&amp;mdash;&lt;strong&gt;MDM&lt;/strong&gt; 2018 (&lt;strong&gt;CORE B&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Toan Nguyen, Duc Kieu, Bao Duong, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Kien Do, Thin Nguyen, and Bac Le. &lt;em&gt;Class-incremental Learning with Causal Relational Replay&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Expert Syst. Appl.&lt;/strong&gt; 250 2024&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bay Vo, Tuong Le, Zhi-Hong Deng, and Bac Le. &lt;em&gt;Mining Top-k Co-occurrence Items with Sequential Pattern&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Expert Syst. Appl.&lt;/strong&gt; 85 2017&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;preprint&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Preprint&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#preprint&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Buang Zhang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Xiangfei Qiu, Chenjuan Guo, Jilin Hu, Aoying Zhou, Christian S. Jensen, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;An Encode-then-Decompose Approach to Unsupervised Time Series Anomaly Detection on Contaminated Training Data&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duc Kieu, Kien Do, Tuan Hoang, Thao Minh Le, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Dang Nguyen, and Thin Nguyen. &lt;em&gt;Universal Multi-Domain Translation via Diffusion Routers&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Huy Le, Nhat Chung, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Jingkang Yang, and Ngan Le. &lt;em&gt;UNO: Unifying One-stage Video Scene Graph Generation via Object-Centric Visual Representation Learning&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Nghiem Thanh Pham, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Duc-Manh Nguyen, Son Ha Xuan, Nghia Duong-Trung, and Danh Le-Phuoc. &lt;em&gt;SLM-Bench: A Comprehensive Benchmark of Small Language Models on Environmental Impact&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Huy Le, Nhat Chung, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Anh Nguyen, and Ngan Le. &lt;em&gt;BiMa: Towards Biases Mitigation for Text-Video Retrieval via Scene Element Guidance&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Duc Kieu, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Peng Han, Bin Yang, Christian S. Jensen, and Bac Le. &lt;em&gt;TEAM: Topological Evolution-aware Framework for Traffic Forecasting&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chenjuan Guo, Ronghui Xu, Bin Yang, Ye Yuan, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Yan Zhao, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Efficient Stochastic Routing in Path-Centric Uncertain Road Networks&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Miao Zhang, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;QCore: Data-Efficient, On-Device Continual Calibration for Quantized Models&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Huy Le, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Anh Nguyen, and Ngan Le. &lt;em&gt;WAVER: Writing-style Agnostic Video Retrieval via Distilling Vision-Language Models Through Open-Vocabulary Knowledge&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, Miao Zhang, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;LightTS: Lightweight Time Series Classification with Adaptive Ensemble Distillation&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Bin Yang, Chenjuan Guo, Christian S. Jensen, Yan Zhao, Feiteng Huang, and Kai Zheng. &lt;em&gt;Robust and Explainable Autoencoders for Time Series Outlier Detection&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Xuanyi Dong, Shirui Pan, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;Triformer: Triangular, Variable-Specific Attentions for Long Sequence Multivariate Time Series Forecasting&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Razvan-Gabriel Cirstea, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Shirui Pan, and Bin Yang. &lt;em&gt;Towards Spatio-Temporal Aware Traffic Time Series Forecasting&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Chenjuan Guo, Feiteng Huang, Kai Zheng, Bin Yang, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;Unsupervised Time Series Outlier Detection with Diversity-Driven Convolutional Ensembles&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yan Zhao, Liwei Deng, Xuanhao Chen, Chenjuan Guo, Bin Yang, &lt;strong&gt;Tung Kieu&lt;/strong&gt;, Feiteng Huang, Torben Bach Pedersen, Kai Zheng, and Christian S. Jensen. &lt;em&gt;A Comparative Study on Unsupervised Anomaly Detection for Time Series: Experiments and Analysis&amp;ndash;Extended Version&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://tungk.github.io/pages/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tungk.github.io/pages/services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;awards&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Awards&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#awards&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Best PC Award in IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering (ICDE)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conferences&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Conferences&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#conferences&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM SIGKDD Conference on Knowledge Discovery and Data Mining (SIGKDD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM SIGMOD Conference on Management of Data (SIGMOD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conference on Neural Information Processing Systems (NEURIPS)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;International Conference on Very Large Data Bases (VLDB)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM Web Conference (TheWebConf)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE International Conference on Data Engineering (ICDE)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM International Conference on Multimedia (MM)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM International Conference on Information and Knowledge Management (CIKM)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE/CVF Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision (WACV)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM SIGSPATIAL International Conference on Advances in Geographic Information Systems (SIGSPATIAL/GIS)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE International Conference on Big Data (BigData)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;International Conference on Advanced Data Mining and Applications (ADMA)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;APWeb-WAIM International Joint Conference on Web and Big Data (APWEB-WAIM)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE International Conference on Mobile Data Management (MDM)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;journals&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Journals&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#journals&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ACM Transactions on Information Systems (TOIS)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (TNNLS)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering (TKDE)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Signal Processing (TSP)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Intelligent Transportation Systems (TITS)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Network Science and Engineering (TNSE)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Transactions on Industrial Informatics (TII)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Data Mining and Knowledge Discovery (DMKD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pattern Recognition&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Neural Networks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Expert Systems with Applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Neural Processing Letters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IEEE Access&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;collaboration&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Collaboration&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#collaboration&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with &lt;em&gt;TADAA!&lt;/em&gt; (in aSTEP project).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with the &lt;em&gt;BioX&lt;/em&gt; (in aSTEP project).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with &lt;em&gt;Huawei&lt;/em&gt; (in Huawei project)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://tungk.github.io/pages/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tungk.github.io/pages/teaching/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;coordination&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Coordination&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#coordination&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Software 7 (SW9).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Software 9 (SW9).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;courses&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Courses&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#courses&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced Algorithms (shared with Prof. Bin Yang and Prof. Chenjuan Guo).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Algorithms and Computability (shared with Prof. Bin Yang, Prof. Dalin Zhang, and Prof. Alvaro Torralba).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Algorithms and Satisfiability (shared with Prof. Bin Yang, Prof. Dalin Zhang, and Prof. Alvaro Torralba).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Introduction to Database Systems (at RMIT University).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Programming Bootcamp (at RMIT University).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Programming Studio (at RMIT University).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Data-intensive Sytems.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Specilization Course in Database/Data Mining.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mobile Data and Location-based Services (shared with Prof. Tiantian Liu).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;supervision&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Supervision&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#supervision&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Software 4 (SW4).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Software 5 (SW5).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Software 6 (SW6).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Specialization course in Database Technology (SpDT).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Master Thesis (shared with Prof. Bin Yang).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-assistant&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Teaching Assistant&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#teaching-assistant&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Algorithms and Data Structures (shared with Sean Bin Yang).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advanced Algorithms (shared with Sean Bin Yang).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Algorithms and Computability (shared with Jákup Odssonur Svöðstein).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Algorithms and Satisfiability (shared with Jákup Odssonur Svöðstein).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;master-students&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Master Students&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#master-students&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos (co-supervised with Prof. Bin Yang)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mik Christensen (co-supervised with Prof. Bin Yang)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;phd-students&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  Ph.D. Students&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;a class=&#34;heading-link&#34; href=&#34;#phd-students&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;i class=&#34;fa-solid fa-link&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; title=&#34;Link to heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&#xD;&#xA;    &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;Link to heading&lt;/span&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;David Campos (co-supervised with Prof. Bin Yang)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
